I am going to show you how to make a Bluetail Fly.
First you're going to take your ice, you pour it into your glass, you're going to add one ounce of gin, have you jigger handy.
Pour your ounce in just like so, you're going to add a half an ounce of blue curacao, this is a blue flavored liqueur, but it has an orange flavor to it.
Then you're going to take some sour mix, so pour that into your concoction as well, and then you're going to shake this up really well.
Get your tin, pour it in just like that, give it a good shake, you're going to grab your glass, pour it in just like that.
It's a nice blueish green flavor, and then you're going to take some soda water and you're going to top it off, just like so.
Give it some fizz, make it all nice and fun.
Add your straw, you can add a cherry or whatever.
If you're a guy you don't have to, if you're a lady throw one in.
And enjoy your Bluetail Fly.